<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Pages of my Stories</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Pages of my Stories</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.127.0</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Danger Of Memories</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/the_danger_of_memories/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/the_danger_of_memories/</guid>
      <description>“Grandpa! Grandpa! Can you tell us another story, pretty please?”
I chuckled, “It’s late kiddos, you need to get yourself to bed.”
“Please? We can’t sleep without your stories!” “Not now guys, it&amp;rsquo;s late.”
“Pleasee?”, they clamoured, giving puppy eyes so overwhelmingly cute that it could melt stone and unwrap poison ivy curled around the coldest of hearts. “Not today”, I said, using every bit of self control I had not to let the cool grasp of logic slip on the hot coals of their cuteness.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Acceptance Our Fault</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/is_acceptance_our_fault/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/is_acceptance_our_fault/</guid>
      <description>Being a Bangladeshi Hindu, our family is one rich in culture and history dating back decades and decades ago. Whenever we introduce others to our traditions through food, rituals, or festivals, there is nothing but amazement and respect shown.
Human curiosity about different cultures expands perspectives, fostering sensitivity, understanding, and greater knowledge of the world. However, there are a large group of people who refuse to show interest in other cultures, solely because of the origin of these cultures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Abuse</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/abuse/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/abuse/</guid>
      <description>“STOP IT!”, I cried, as glass hurled across the room, smashing into the wall with a sharp crack. He turned from his target, paying no attention to me, to find his next weapon, rustling around the dark room with a depraved thirst for anything; anything which could harm, anything which would draw blood. As this monster of a man, nothing but a mere shadow of the man who I thought I knew, stormed around for his next to-be-projectile, I turned around to look at the woman lying on the floor, her gentle hands cradling the sea of red pouring from her marked and bruised forehead.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Digital/Familial Divide</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/digital_familial_divide/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/digital_familial_divide/</guid>
      <description>Esteemed members of the Commonwealth, thank you for all gathering here today to discuss the issues that face the world, and allowing me to speak my piece on what I think that problem is. First of all, I must preface my speech by highlighting that there is not just one issue that is the most important for the world; there are several problems which impact many different demographics, and the answer to this question will probably vary greatly from person to person.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trying to Understand</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/trying_to_understand/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/trying_to_understand/</guid>
      <description>“It’s been a long day”, I mutter to myself as I plop myself down for the day, feeling the fatigue in my bones dissolve into the soft folds of the couch. As I grabbed my beer and my old TV fluttered to life, I sat there, reflecting on the day. My job is one with very few breaks, and times such as these, where I can just be left alone with my own thoughts, are very rare and very welcomed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Versatile Human Voice</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/the_versatile_human_voice/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/the_versatile_human_voice/</guid>
      <description>If you Google the meaning of voice, it will say:
voice (noun) The sound produced in a person’s larynx and uttered through the mouth, such as speech or song. But in contrast, the second definition is as follows:
A particular opinion, or attitude expressed Now, depending on who you are, you may relate to one more than the other. If you are of a more direct disposition, you may immediately associate it with the first definition; the literal meaning of voice; the produced sound.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
